David Martinez Barreiro

0483505742 <u>david@dmbarreiro.com</u> <u>https://dmbarreiro.com</u> <u>https://github.com/dmbarreiro</u> <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidmartinezbarreiro/</u> Maria Theresiastraat, 25 B0202, 3000, Leuven, Belgium

Profile

I am a software engineer passionate about Javascript. I have experience working with the MEAN (MongoDB, Express.js, Angular, Node.js) stack and have a keen interest in design patterns and cloud technologies. I enjoy participating in the open source community, check my github profile (or this automatically generated github resume) and my npm profile. I am keen on learning new technologies and paradigms to make systems and code understandable to people. In the past I worked with operating systems and embedded devices.

Experience

ENGINEER CONSULTANT, AKKA BENELUX – 2013-PRESENT

Provided expertise in high performance embedded environments, operating systems, internet communications and security.

TEST ENGINEER, EKINOPS BELGIUM - 2013-2018

Test plan design, integration testing, system performance analysis (bottle necks), reverse engineering, system API design, validation.

Languages: C, Python.

Tools: SVN, Git

Education

University of Vigo, Vigo, Spain – BS, Telecommunications Engineering, 2005-2009

University of Vigo, Vigo, Spain – MS, Telecommunications Engineering, 2009-2013

Skills

- Javascript/Typescript
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- SQL
- Angular 2+
- Git
- Express.js

- Docker
- CI/CD (CircleCI, TravisCI)
- Firebase/Google Cloud